(traffic whirring)
(girl shouting)
(Spice Girls cheering)
(Spice Girls chattering)
- Wannabe!
♪ Gotta get with my friends ♪
♪ If you wannabe me lover ♪
♪ You gotta get with my friends ♪
♪ Make it last forever ♪
♪ Friendship never ends ♪
- What went on there, then?
- Started too high.
- Come on, come on.
- Get it, get it, get it!
(heels clipping)
(papers rustling)
(Mel B laughing)
♪ Yeah, I'll tell you what I want ♪
♪ What I really, really want ♪
♪ So tell me what you want,
what you really, really want ♪
♪ I'll tell you what I want,
what I really, really want ♪
♪ So tell me what you want,
what you really, really want ♪
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
♪ I wanna really, really,
really wanna zigazig ah ♪
♪ If you want my future, forget my past ♪
♪ If you wanna get with
me, better make it fast ♪
♪ Now don't go wasting my precious time ♪
♪ Get your act together
we could be just fine ♪
♪ I'll tell you what I want,
what I really, really want ♪
♪ So tell me what you want,
what you really, really want ♪
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
♪ I wanna really, really,
really wanna zigazig ah ♪
♪ If you wanna be my lover,
you gotta get with my friends ♪
♪ Make it last forever,
friendship never ends ♪
♪ If you wanna be my lover,
you have got to give ♪
♪ Taking is too easy, but
that's the way it is ♪
♪ What do you think about
that, now you know how I feel ♪
♪ Say, you can handle my
love, are you for real ♪
♪ I won't be hasty, I'll give you a try ♪
♪ If you really bug me
then I'll say goodbye ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll tell you what I want ♪
♪ What I really, really want ♪
♪ So tell me what you want,
what you really, really want ♪
♪ I wanna, I wanna, I wanna, I wanna ♪
♪ I wanna really, really,
really wanna zigazig ah ♪
♪ If you wanna be my lover,
you gotta get with my friends ♪
♪ Make it last forever,
friendship never ends ♪
♪ If you wanna be my lover,
you have got to give ♪
♪ Taking is too easy, but
that's the way it is ♪
♪ So, here's a story from A to Z ♪
♪ You wanna get with me,
you gotta listen carefully ♪
♪ We got Em in the place
who likes it in your face ♪
♪ You got G like MC who likes it on a ♪
♪ Easy V doesn't come for
free, she's a real lady ♪
♪ And as for me, ah you'll see ♪
♪ Slam your body down
and wind it all around ♪
♪ If you wanna be my lover,
you gotta get with my friends ♪
♪ Make it last forever,
friendship never ends ♪
♪ If you wanna be my lover,
you have got to give ♪
♪ Taking is too easy, but
that's the way it is ♪
♪ If you wanna be my lover ♪
♪ You gotta, you gotta,
you gotta, you gotta ♪
♪ You gotta slam, slam, slam, slam ♪
♪ Slam your body down
and wind it all around ♪
♪ Slam your body down and zigazig ah ♪
(upbeat instrumental)
♪ If you wanna be my lover ♪
(girls squealing)
(bus engine rumbling)